Look. Our first mail.
瞧,我们的第一份邮件.
Apply for your new credit card today!
今天去申请新的信用卡.
Why are you getting these?
你怎么会收到这些信?
Because, Michael, I am an ideal consumer.
因为,Michael,我是个理想的顾客.
These people dream about me.
这些人做梦都想跟我打交道.
They drool over me.
简直是垂涎三尺.
Under30, underemployed,
我不到30岁,工作不理想,
works at night for a minimum wage in a copy place.
晚上在复印社干活,拿的是最低工资.
I don't have cash. I need their cards.
我没有现金.所以我需要他们的卡.
You want some?
你要来点儿吗?
Glad that's not scotch.
很高兴那不是苏格兰威士忌.
What's got you so down?
你怎么闷闷不乐的?
Jeannette called me at work and broke up with me.
Jeannette上班时间给我打电话提出跟我分手.
Ouch.
Yeah, well, between you and me,
Yeah, well,我跟你私下说,
it was just a matter of time.
这是迟早的问题.
How come?
怎么会?
I'm not ambitious.
我胸无大志.
I am going around in circles.
我来回地绕圈子.
And I don't have a life plan.
我没有人生规划.
Does Jeannette?
Jeannette呢?
Oh, Jeannette has a very detailed schedule.
Oh, Jeannette有非常详细的计划.
How's the movie?
电影进展如何了?
Good. I'm just going out to shoot.
很好.我现在正要出去拍摄.
Listen, Danny,
听着,Danny,
there's an experimental film at MIT on Saturday.
周六在麻省理工学院放一部实验影片.
Do you want to come Saturday evening before you go to work?
周六晚上上班前你想去看吗?
Are you bringing Lisa?
你带Lisa去吗?
-Yep.  -Does she have a friend?
-是的. -她有朋友吗?
How quickly they forget!
他们忘得可真快!